export default {
  name: "Spanish Words: Basics",
  cards: [
  { front: "none", back: "ninguno" },
  { front: "Tuesday", back: "(el) martes" },
  { front: "west", back: "oeste" },
  { front: "more", back: "más" },
  { front: "suddenly", back: "de repente" },
  { front: "it", back: "eso" },
  { front: "who", back: "quién" },
  { front: "already", back: "ya" },
  { front: "July", back: "julio" },
  { front: "how", back: "cómo" },
  { front: "today", back: "hoy" },
  { front: "child", back: "(el) niño" },
  { front: "if", back: "si" },
  { front: "they", back: "ellos" },
  { front: "love", back: "(el) amor" },
  { front: "when", back: "cuándo" },
  { front: "Friday", back: "(el) viernes" },
  { front: "very", back: "muy" },
  { front: "big brother", back: "(el) hermano mayor" },
  { front: "year", back: "(el) año" },
  { front: "everybody", back: "todo el mundo" },
  { front: "all", back: "todos" },
  { front: "night", back: "(la) noche" },
  { front: "spring", back: "(la) primavera" },
  { front: "Wednesday", back: "(el) miércoles" },
  { front: "December", back: "diciembre" },
  { front: "January", back: "enero" },
  { front: "east", back: "este" },
  { front: "now", back: "ahora" },
  { front: "little sister", back: "(la) hermana menor" },
  { front: "morning (9:00-11:00)", back: "(la) mañana" },
  { front: "we", back: "nosotros" },
  { front: "sex", back: "(el) sexo" },
  { front: "always", back: "siempre" },
  { front: "and", back: "y" },
  { front: "parents", back: "(los) padres" },
  { front: "May", back: "mayo" },
  { front: "far", back: "lejos" },
  { front: "evening", back: "(la) noche" },
  { front: "husband", back: "(el) marido" },
  { front: "most", back: "el más/la más" },
  { front: "dad", back: "(el) papá" },
  { front: "you (plural)", back: "ustedes" },
  { front: "beside", back: "junto a" },
  { front: "below", back: "abajo" },
  { front: "he", back: "él" },
  { front: "big sister", back: "(la) hermana mayor" },
  { front: "summer", back: "(el) verano" },
  { front: "hour", back: "(la) hora" },
  { front: "then", back: "entonces" },
  { front: "that", back: "ese" },
  { front: "day", back: "(el) día" },
  { front: "mother", back: "(la) madre" },
  { front: "Monday", back: "(el) lunes" },
  { front: "not", back: "no" },
  { front: "although", back: "aunque" },
  { front: "little brother", back: "(el) hermano menor" },
  { front: "she", back: "ella" },
  { front: "Thursday", back: "(el) jueves" },
  { front: "above", back: "arriba" },
  { front: "actually", back: "en realidad" },
  { front: "Saturday", back: "(el) sábado" },
  { front: "week", back: "(la) semana" },
  { front: "this", back: "este" },
  { front: "or", back: "o" },
  { front: "son", back: "(el) hijo" },
  { front: "friend", back: "(el) amigo" },
  { front: "morning (6:00-9:00)", back: "(la) mañana" },
  { front: "where", back: "dónde" },
  { front: "month", back: "(el) mes" },
  { front: "right", back: "derecha" },
  { front: "I", back: "yo" },
  { front: "June", back: "junio" },
  { front: "less", back: "menos" },
  { front: "woman", back: "(la) mujer" },
  { front: "front", back: "frente" },
  { front: "close", back: "cerca" },
  { front: "mum", back: "(la) mamá" },
  { front: "August", back: "agosto" },
  { front: "but", back: "pero" },
  { front: "inside", back: "dentro" },
  { front: "girlfriend", back: "(la) novia" },
  { front: "girl", back: "(la) niña" },
  { front: "April", back: "abril" },
  { front: "outside", back: "fuera" },
  { front: "kiss", back: "(el) beso" },
  { front: "February", back: "febrero" },
  { front: "back (position)", back: "atrás" },
  { front: "really", back: "realmente" },
  { front: "afternoon", back: "(la) tarde" },
  { front: "September", back: "septiembre" },
  { front: "autumn", back: "(el) otoño" },
  { front: "wife", back: "(la) esposa" },
  { front: "yesterday", back: "ayer" },
  { front: "which", back: "cuál" },
  { front: "second (time)", back: "(el) segundo" },
  { front: "immediately", back: "inmediatamente" },
  { front: "because", back: "porque" },
  { front: "tomorrow", back: "mañana" },
  { front: "why", back: "por qué" },
  { front: "often", back: "a menudo" },
  { front: "together", back: "juntos" },
  { front: "minute", back: "(el) minuto" },
  { front: "March", back: "marzo" },
  { front: "midnight", back: "(la) medianoche" },
  { front: "boyfriend", back: "(el) novio" },
  { front: "winter", back: "(el) invierno" },
  { front: "boy", back: "(el) niño" },
  { front: "what", back: "qué" },
  { front: "November", back: "noviembre" },
  { front: "father", back: "(el) padre" },
  { front: "other", back: "otro" },
  { front: "again", back: "de nuevo" },
  { front: "man", back: "(el) hombre" },
  { front: "October", back: "octubre" },
  { front: "Sunday", back: "(el) domingo" },
  { front: "you (singular)", back: "tú" },
  { front: "north", back: "norte" },
  { front: "daughter", back: "(la) hija" },
  { front: "left", back: "izquierda" },
  { front: "every", back: "cada" },
  { front: "here", back: "aquí" },
  { front: "there", back: "allá" },
  { front: "south", back: "sur" },
  { front: "noon", back: "(el) mediodía" },
  ],
};
